<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Decadents</name>
	<author>gilith59</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>gilith.decadents</packageId>
	<modVersion>1.0.0</modVersion>
	<description>Introducing Decadents, three drug-dependent xenotypes that must consume specific substances to survive. Each xenotype has unique mechanics, specialized rest chambers, and connectable buildings that grant permanent bonuses.

🍺 Le Festoyeur (The Reveler)
A beer-loving barbarian warrior who thrives on alcohol and close combat. Uses a Beer Casket for rest and can connect Beer Amplifiers and Ambrosia Infusers for permanent stat bonuses.

💉 Le Baron (The Baron)
A high-speed stimulant addict with enhanced consciousness and movement. Uses a Stim Casket and connects Wake-up Injectors, Go-juice Pumps, Flake Dispensers, and Yayo Refiners for combat and work bonuses.

🌿 Le Rêveur (The Dreamer)
A mystical psychedelic user with enhanced psychic abilities and social skills. Uses a Dream Casket and connects Smokeleaf Vaporizers and Psychite Diffusers for peaceful and intellectual bonuses.

Key Features:
- Three unique xenotypes with custom resource systems (Beergen, Stimgen, Dreamgen)
- Specialized rest caskets that consume drugs to restore resources
- Connectable buildings that apply permanent hediff bonuses
- Unique gene combinations for each playstyle
- Full drug tolerance and no addiction to their respective substances
- Inspired by Sanguophage deathrest mechanics

Transform your colony with these substance-dependent beings and master the art of drug production to keep your Decadents thriving!

Requires: Biotech DLC</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
			<displayName>Biotech</displayName>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
